<resources>
    <string name="app_name">project_2</string>
    <string name="plant_plus">Plant Plus</string>
    <string name="todo">flower</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">MainActivity</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="emailToast">You must enter email to register!</string>

    <string name="Marigold">Marigold health benefits:
Soothes skin and treats skin diseases
Reduces inflammation
Strong antibacterial and antiseptic properties
Strengthens eyes</string>

    <string name="Catnip">
        Catnip is a fun plant for cats. Most cats are attracted to the plant and will roll around near it since its aroma acts as a stimulant.
    </string>
    <string name="Gingko">
        gingko is one of the oldest homeopathic plants and a key herb in Chinese medicine. The leaves are used to create capsules, tablets, and extracts, and when dried, can be consumed as a tea.

    </string>
    <string name="Turmeric">
       <b> Turmeric could be beneficial for:</b>
pain caused by inflammatory diseases, like arthritis.
preventing cancer.
stopping DNA mutations.
several skin diseases.
    </string>

    <string name="Moonflowers">
Evening primrose flowers are also called moonflower because they bloom as the sun begins to set. People often say they smell like lemons.
    </string>

    <string name="privacypolicy">
        <b>Privacy Policy of plant plus, Inc.</b>
          \n\n
       <p> Plant plus, Inc.(\"We\" or \"us\"or\"ours\" as applicable) takes great care in ensuring that any transmission of
        your personal information remains private and is not disclosed in an unauthorized way. We respect the privacy
        of every person who uses the mobile application, including related features, products and services (collectively
        referred to as the \"Platform\") and we are committed to a safe online experience for our users. Although the platform
        is not designed to collect material personal data, we feel that it is important to explain the information we collect,
        what we do with it, and describe the rights you may have in relation to the data. We also respect the privacy of everyone
        who uses the services we provide from the platform or deals with the platform or from us to use the services provided
        (whether through the platform or not) (the \"service\" or \"services\") or whose personal information may be processed as a
        result of the use of others. For services.</p>
        \n
        \n\n

        <b>WHAT IS THE PURPOSE OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY\?</b>
        \n\n

        <p>This privacy statement (\"Privacy Policy\") explains our collection of any personal information that we may obtain about you
        from you or a third party and the purposes for which we may process such information. This Privacy Policy also sets out your
        rights in respect to our processing of your personal information. The purpose of this Privacy Policy is also to comport to applicable
            data privacy laws and, if applicable, the \"DP Laws\" (as defined near the end of this Privacy Policy).</p>
      \n
        <p>This Privacy Policy informs you of the nature of the information that is collected and processed by us and how you can request that
            we delete, update, transfers and/or provide you with access to it.</p>
        \n

        <p>This Privacy Policy is intended to help you make an informed decision when using the Platform and our Services and/or to understand
        how your information may be processed by us as a result of your use of and the function of the Platform and Services. Please read
        this Privacy Policy carefully so that you understand it. Please note that when using the Platform it should be read in conjunction
            with our Terms of Service, as may be updated from time to time.</p>
        \n

        <p>Please also note that this Privacy Policy only applies to the use of your personal information obtained by us, it does NOT apply to
            your personal information that is collected during your communications with third parties.</p>
         \n
        \n

        <b>Who is the PLANT PLUS, INC. What do we do\?</b>
         \n\n
        <p>Plant plus, Inc. It is an application for a graduation project established in Jordan. We are the data controller responsible for
            processing your personal information through the platform.</p>
        \n \n

        <b>HOW TO CONTACT US\?</b>
                 \n\n
        <p>If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or want to take any action with respect to your personal information as set out
            in this Privacy Policy, you must contact us by: </p>
        \n
        Sending an Email to: Project.herb2\@gmail.com
        \n
         \n
        <b>WHY DO WE COLLECT YOUR DATA AND WHAT DO WE COLLECT\?</b>
         \n \n
        Our primary goal in collecting personal information from you is to:
        \n
            \t\t1) verify your identity.\n
            \t\t2) help us deliver the Services and provide your ability to use the Platform actively.\n
            \t\t3) improve, develop and market new Services.\n
            \t\t4) carry out requests made by you on the Platform or in relation to our Services.\n
            \t\t5) investigate or settle inquiries or disputes.\n
            \t\t6) comply with any applicable law.\n
            \t\t7) enforce our agreements with you.\n
            \t\t8) protect the rights, property or safety of us or third parties, including our other customers, subscribers and users of the Platform
            or our Services.\n
            \t\t9) provide support for the provision of our Services.\n
            \t\t10) use as otherwise permitted by law.\n
                \n
 \n
        To undertake these goals, we may collect the following personal information related to our users:
         \n
            *Name \n
            *E-mail address \n
            *IP Address saved by our web server logs \n
            *Third-party service vendor data, as collected by such third-party\'s at our request \n
            *Other data collected using Google Analytics by Google, Inc. \n
         \n

        We may also collect information about your use of the Platform including: \n
         \n
            *Electronic communications protocols \n
            *Web pages visited \n
            *Cookies \n
            *User preferences \n
            * User privileges \n
            *Other information relevant to provision of the Services \n
            *Other information as may be requested by us from you in relation to provision of the Services \n
            *Third-party monitoring related to web traffic \n
            

</string>
    <string name="terms_conditions">
        <b>Terms of Use</b>
        \n
        \n
        Plant plus, Inc., its affiliate entities and any successor entity, (collectively, \"Provider\") maintains the PlantSnap mobile application,
        including related features, products, and services (collectively, the \"Service\"). You should read these Terms of Use (this \"Agreement\")
        carefully before using the Service. Access to and use of the Service is subject to the terms and conditions set forth below, and your
        use of the Service constitutes your acceptance of this Agreement. If you do not agree to this Agreement, you should not use the Service.
        Provider may revise this Agreement from time to time. Although Provider may include a notice on the home page of the Service that the
        Agreement has been modified, such notice may not remain in place for any extended period of time. Accordingly, you should review the
        Agreement as posted on the Service from time to time. Using the Service after any revised Agreement has been posted will constitute
        your acceptance of the revised terms.
         \n
        \n
        <b>1. Purpose of the Service</b>
         \n
        The PlantSnap Service helps you identify plants, flowers and trees through image recognition technology. We use photographs submitted
        by you to provide the Service. You acknowledge that Provider disclaims any responsibility for, or liability related to, your use of
        the Service (see \"Disclaimer of Warranties\" below). You may never rely on the Service to determine whether any plant, flower, tree
        \or any other substance is safe to eat or otherwise consume and Provider hereby specifically disclaims any responsibility for, or
        liability related to, your use of the Service for this purpose.
        \n
        \n
        <b>2. Use of the Service</b>
        \n
        Use of the Service may be available through a compatible Internet browser or mobile device and may require network connections and
        software. You agree that you are solely responsible for these requirements, including any applicable changes, updates and fees as well
        as the terms of your agreement with your mobile device and telecommunications provider. You are only entitled to access and use the
        Service for lawful purposes. You agree that Provider may use your feedback, suggestions, or ideas in any way, including in future
        modifications of the Service, other products or services, advertising or marketing materials. You grant Provider a perpetual,
        worldwide, fully-transferable, sub-licensable, irrevocable, fully paid-up, royalty-free license to use the feedback you provide
        to Provider in any way. You further agree that you will not: (i) use any robot, spider, scraper, deep link or other similar automated
        data gathering or extraction tools, program, algorithm or methodology to access, acquire, copy or monitor the Service or any portion
        of the Service; (ii) post or transmit any file which contains viruses, worms, Trojan horses or any other contaminating or destructive
        features, or that otherwise interfere with the proper working of Provider or the Service; or (iii) attempt to decipher, decompile,
        disassemble, or reverse-engineer any of the software comprising or in any way making up a part of the Service.
         \n
        \n
        <b>3. Lawful Use; Use by Minors</b>
        \n
        Your access to and use of the Service is subject to all applicable international, federal, state and local laws and regulations.
        You represent and warrant that you will not use the Service in any manner or for any purposes that are unlawful or prohibited by this
        Agreement. The Service is not targeted towards, nor intended for use by, anyone under the age of 18. By using the Service, you
        represent and warrant that you are 18 years of age or older. If you are not at least 18 years of age, do not use, access, or
        register for the Service. Provider reserves the right to terminate your membership in the event that Provider becomes aware you
        are under 18.
        \n
        \n
        <b>4. User Accounts</b>
        \n
        To post photographs and otherwise use the Service, you must first register by creating a User Account. You should take measures to maintain
        and preserve the confidentiality of the username and password associated with your User Account, and you must notify Provider promptly
        of any unauthorized use or suspected breach of security of your User Account. Provider shall not be liable for any losses that may
        result from any unauthorized use of your User Account or failure to maintain appropriate confidentiality measures. You agree not to
        disclose your password to any third party and to take sole responsibility for any activities or actions under your User Account,
        whether or not you have authorized such activities or actions. Provider owns your User Account credentials and may revoke or change
        them at any time.
         \n
        \n
        <b>5. Rights you Grant to Provider</b>
        \n
        By submitting User Content to Provider through the Service, you grant a non-exclusive, sub-licenseable, perpetual, worldwide license
        to any and all User Content to Provider and any affiliate and successor entities for the purpose of providing the Service, or any
        similar services at Provider\'s, its affiliate\'s or successor\'s sole discretion. Provider may use and store the User Content, but only
        to provide the Service to you or related to its license provided by you as stated above. By submitting this User Content to Provider,
        you represent that you are entitled to submit it to Provider for use for this purpose, without any obligation by Provider to pay any
        fees or other limitations.
        \n \n

        <b>6>. Intellectual Property Rights</b>
        \n
        Unless otherwise noted, all text, images, graphics, photographs, video clips, designs, icons, sounds, information, data, and other
        materials appearing on the Service which are not User Content (the \"Provider Content\") and all methods, methodologies, procedures,
        processes, know-how, software, algorithms, techniques, and other technology (the \"Technology\") displayed, used, or incorporated
        on the Service by Provider are copyrights, trademarks, service marks, trade secrets, or other intellectual property or proprietary
        content owned or licensed by Provider. You may use the available Provider Content and Technology only for your own personal use and
        internal business purposes, but you may not reverse-engineer or decompile any of the Technology. You may print a copy of available
        Provider Content solely for such purposes, but you may not remove any copyright, trademark or other notice displayed on the
        corresponding webpage or print-out. You may not use the available Provider Content and Technology on behalf of any third party
        or as part of a managed service. You may not distribute, publish, transmit, modify, create derivative works from, or in any way
        exploit, any of the available Provider Content and Technology, in whole or in part, for any purpose without the express written
        permission of Provider or the respective owner. Nothing in this Agreement shall be construed as granting any permission
        (except as set forth in this paragraph), right, or license in any of the Provider Content or Technology. All intellectual property
        rights are fully reserved by Provider and any third-party owners of those rights.
        \n\n
        <b>7. Use of \"Cookies\" and Similar Tools</b>
        \n
        You understand and agree that Provider may store information on your computer in the form of a \"cookie\" or similar tool for
        purposes of improving the functionality of the Service.
        \n\n
        <b>8. Limitations on Liability</b>
        \n
        In no event shall Provider be liable to you or any other person or entity for any direct, indirect, incidental, special,
        consequential, punitive, or other such damages, including but not limited to any damages associated with: (i) loss of goodwill,
        profits, business interruption, or data, or other such losses; (ii) your inability to use the Service, any unauthorized use of the
        Service, or any function of the Service or failure of the Service to function; (iii) the provision of or failure to provide any
        service though the Service; (iv) errors or inaccuracies in the User Content, Provider Content, Technology, or any advertising or
        other information, software, products, services, and related graphics used, viewed, or obtained through the Service; or (v) any
        property loss including damage to your computer or computer system caused by viruses or other harmful components encountered during
        or on account of access to or use of this Service or any third-party website linked to this Service. These limitations of liability
        shall apply regardless of the form of action, whether based in contract, negligence, strict liability, other tort, or otherwise,
        and even if Provider has been advised of the possibility of any particular damages. To the extent you allege or assert any damages
        associated with the Service which are not excluded
        \n

</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="account">Account</string>
    <string name="edit_profile">Edit Profile</string>
    <string name="change_password">Change password</string>
    <string name="change_language">Change language</string>
    <string name="Select_language">Select language.... </string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="terms">Terms &amp; Conditions</string>
    <string name="remember">Make sure you remember your password</string>
    <string name="current_password">Your current password</string>
    <string name="new_password">Your new password</string>
    <string name="confirm_password">Confirm password</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="username">User name</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="update_profile">Update Profile</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="create">Create New Account</string>
    <string name="choose">choose your account type</string>
    <string name="herbalist">Herbalist Account</string>
    <string name="user">User Account</string>
    <string name="have_accepted">I have accepted the</string>
    <string name="signup">Sign UP</string>
    <string name="signin">Sign In</string>
    <string name="welcome">welcome</string>
    <string name="forget">Forgot Password?</string>
    <string name="add_plant">Add Plant</string>
    <string name="confirm_plant">Confirm Plants</string>
    <string name="logout">Log Out</string>
    <string name="chats">Chats</string>
    <string name="herbalists">Herbalists</string>
    <string name="message">Message</string>
    <string name="fruit">Fruit</string>
    <string name="leaf">Leaf</string>
    <string name="flower">Flower</string>
    <string name="trees">Trees</string>
    <string name="seeds">Seeds</string>
    <string name="roots">Roots</string>
    <string name="plant_name">Plant Name</string>
    <string name="symptoms">Symptoms treated by the plant</string>
    <string name="select_symptoms">Select Symptoms</string>
    <string name="description">Description</string>
    <string name="parts">Parts of plant that use</string>
    <string name="did">Did you know</string>
    <string name="add">Add</string>
    <string name="update_plant">Update Plant</string>
    <string name="update">Update</string>
    <string name="accept">Accept</string>
    <string name="reject">Reject</string>
    <string name="delete">delete</string>
    <string name="fill">Fill your email and we will sent you  a link to change your password</string>
    <string name="get_new">Get Your New Password</string>
    <string name="Dont_have">Don\'t have an account\?</string>
    <string name="register">Register now</string>
    <string name="search">Search</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="search_name">Search for name</string>
    <string name="search_symptoms">search for symptoms</string>
    <string name="clear_all">Clear All</string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>
    <string name="plant_exists">The plant already exists. Do you want to modify the data?</string>
    <string name="admin_confirmation">"The plant has been add but it need for the admin confirmation…"</string>
    <string name="delete_plant">Do you want to delete the plant?</string>
    <string name="yes">YES</string>
    <string name="no">NO</string>
    <string name="take_photo">Take Photo</string>
    <string name="choose_gallery">Choose from gallery</string>

    <string name="Empty_plant_name">Empty plant name</string>
    <string name="Empty_symptoms">Empty symptoms</string>
    <string name="Empty_location">Empty location</string>

    <string name="Empty_description">Empty description</string>
    <string name="Empty_information">Empty information</string>

    <string name="username_required">username required!</string>
    <string name="email_required">email required!</string>
    <string name="valid_email">Enter valid email!</string>
    <string name="Empty_password">Empty password</string>
    <string name="signup_failed">sign up failed</string>
    <string name="signin_failed">sign in failed</string>
    <string name="Fill_information">Fill in all information</string>
    <string name="Check_email">Check your email to reset password</string>
    <string name="Try_Again">Try Again ! Something wrong happened!</string>
    <string name="Error_password">Error password, not updated</string>
    <string name="Password_mismatching">Password mismatching</string>
    <string name="Password_incorrect">Current Password incorrect</string>
    <string name="Password_updated">Password updated successfully</string>
    <string name="Profile_updated">Profile updated successfully</string>
    <string name="plant_added">plant added successfully</string>
    <string name="Plant_deleted">Plant deleted successfully</string>
    <string name="Plant_updated">Plant updated successfully</string>
    <string name="all_fields">Please enter all fields.</string>
    <string name="Sending_image">Sending Image</string>
    <string name="Please_wait">Please wait…</string>
    <string name="gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="Select_image">Select Image</string>
    <string name="write_message">write your message first…</string>
    <string name="Image_successfully">Image Sent Successfully…</string>
    <string name="error">Error</string>


    <string name="fatigue">Fatigue</string>
    <string name="fever">Fever</string>
    <string name="stomachache">Stomachache</string>
    <string name="headache">Headache</string>
    <string name="nausea">Nausea</string>
    <string name="skin">Skin irritation</string>
    <string name="indigestion">Indigestion</string>
    <string name="infections">Infections and ulcers</string>
    <string name="diarrhea">Diarrhea</string>
    <string name="constipation">Constipation</string>
    <string name="colds">Colds</string>

    <string name="levant">Levant</string>
    <string name="Arab_Maghreb">The Arab Maghreb</string>
    <string name="Arabian_Peninsula">The Arabian Peninsula</string>
    <string name="Latin_america">Latin america</string>
    <string name="Australia">Australia</string>
    <string name="Europe">Europe</string>
    <string name="Africa">Africa</string>
    <string name="Middle_Atlantic">Middle Atlantic</string>
    <string name="Western_Indian">Western Indian Ocean</string>
    <string name="West_Asia">West Asia</string>
    <string name="Pacific">Pacific</string>
    <string name="North_Amarica">North Amarica</string>
    <string name="South_America">South America</string>
    <string name="Select_location">Select location</string>
    <string name="Place_origin">Place of origin</string>
    <string name="approved">Plant has been approved by the admin</string>
    <string name="disapproval">Plant has been disapproval by the admin</string>
    <string name="send_email">Email has been sent to herbalist</string>
    <string name="searchname">There are no herb with that name or the name typed wrong, try again or you can find another herb in herb list.</string>
    <string name="searchsymptoms">There is no information currently  available about herbal treatment for these symptoms, please, ask our herbalists by using send a message</string>
    <string name="searchherbalist">There are no herbalist with that name or the name typed wrongly, try again or you can find another herbalist in herbalists list</string>



</resources>